[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "I should plug your book because otherwise there isn't any reason you have to come out, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "How can you say that with a straight face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "I am a uniter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Did you get the tweeted picture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "But finally it explodes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Maybe I could've cared in there in a bit just calm things a bit and been less polarizing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "I was definitely too nice to Hillary Clinton.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "But you never supported Chris Christie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "I mean do you have feelings like Glenn Beck?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "I just told you.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Glenn Beck"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Are there any times you've gone too far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "You don't think you've ever gone too far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 111, "question": "But what do you say -- let's try to be serious for a moment, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "I am being totally ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "... part of the problem, right?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "I am not -- you're part of the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "I mean is it almost exactly the same thing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "OULTER: Well, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["MSNBC"]}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "What's your point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "My point is you're never going to get a scandal against the Democrat broken by MSNBC.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "What do you think of the Chris Christie scandal so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "I think it's the most boring scandal of my entire life.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "... is not a very serious story?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "That I am massively opposed to Chris Christie because he had his temporary sent an appointee, vote for amnesty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Is that helpful to the GOP's chances of beating Hillary Clinton if she runs in 2016?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I don't think he was electable.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"], "ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"], "PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Thoughts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I'm totally against the legalization of pot and not one of these it should be legal for adults but not for kid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Which word isn't true in all that is said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "During -- well I'm going through it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "What isn't true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "First.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What part of the word he said is not true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "That ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["90 percent"]}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBZ", ":", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Or the fact that it's no more dangerous scientifically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "The incarceration figures is -- are ridiculous because 90 percent of those are plea bargain, they catch the guys with six kilos of heroin will plea bargain you down to pot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Why do you keep saying that's untrue and not explain why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "And that -- well I keep trying to when you keep interrupting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Are you intoxicated now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I'm drunk right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Have you ever smoked pot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Wait.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Have you ever smoked pot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "No, I haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Never in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Almost none of my friends have because their athletes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", ":", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "How many potheads do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "And interrogate (ph) a lot of them -- well look potheads can still get the pot they're probably self medicating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Why, why for commerce?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ",", "WRB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Because potheads are incapable of following simple instructions and getting a job done.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "But would be mean by pothead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Was when I move to a new place in California and there was a pool and the pool guy didn't, you know, I come back then it's four feet down it's color covered with green mold.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "What do you mean by a pothead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Everyone knows what a pothead is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "What is it mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Its' not smoking pot one time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "So how much are you assuming a pothead takes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "So like a heavy drinker or a heavy smoker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "No heavy smokers work all night and then die young saving the Social Security System money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "You accept that people can overdose on too much alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well, everything dies eventually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Is he right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "You wouldn't take issue with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 432, "question": "So, you would rather they would chain smoking and heavy drinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I'm just saying, if you care about the productivity...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "One cigarette or two?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Some people are addict.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "That's hilarious but could we also point out that the first e-mail you read during the break was from your publicist telling you let her talk, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "She's from Texas.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Are you dissing the entire State of Texas right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "I love Texas.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "So what do you make of Harvey Weinstein making a stand against the NRA?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Does he know the NRA is not a person and cannot have been born.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"], "PERSON": ["Harvey Weinstein"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "What is wrong with people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Yes, OK, give the money back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Why would that make anything better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "NN", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Because it's utter hypocrisy otherwise.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "You're absolutely 100 percent wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", ":", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "How do you explain that you have similar percentages of a population who are believed to have some form of mental illness in the UK, in Australia, in Japan, in Germany, and yet because there is no availability of guns, they do not have the gun violence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Look, people -- countries are different, demographics are different.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["UK"], "LOCATION": ["Australia", "Japan", "Germany"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Ozzy, what are the moments for you to get back with Sabbath to have this album to come out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "It's been one of the most -- I'm producing all the years of my whole career.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "What was the last meal you cook, Sharon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Don't be ridiculous.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "IN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Pretty special, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "It is special and its well-deserved too, you know, my goodness and they've all paid their dues over and over and over again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 660, "question": "What went on there Ozzy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "Well ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "How did you feel when you watched that Ozzy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Well, it's out of my control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "Did you fear that this might end the marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "It was more hurt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Do you think you'll be able to avoid falling off the rails again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "I can't say -- I can't ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "``", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Or this is going to live with you forever, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "I cannot say yes and I can't say no because it's cunning, powerful, and bad because my head will say, \"Gone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "How did you were back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "Well, It was very difficult, she was really upset with me, you know, and I don't blame her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "What was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "Ozzy came around to have a talk at the hotel that I was staying at and I told him -- no, I was like.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "What was the moment for you Sharon when you thought, \"I'm going to take him back\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "''", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "You know what, it's -- you put up this front because it's what you should do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 805, "question": "What's going on with young Mr. Bieber?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 806, "answer": "You know, I think that some of it is just his age.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 820, "question": "I mean it's just incredible that he did so well, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 821, "answer": "We did the quivering myth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 837, "question": "But Kelly is like a mini me, isn't she really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 838, "answer": "She is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kelly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 849, "question": "Are you going to carry on new gadgets and stones in the '70s?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 850, "answer": "It's up in the air.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 851, "question": "I'm going for it but what we all doing we're going to do a tour of -- where am I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 852, "answer": "Oh my gosh, you're going everywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "You still get on together as family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "It was great better than ever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 871, "question": "As a huge Beatles fan, what do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 872, "answer": "I think it's great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "''", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ":", "PRP$", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "''", "."], "qSentId": 877, "question": "Amazing isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 878, "answer": "But I can remember the first time I heard \"She Loves You\", I was looking in -- my when I listened and I asked him with the transistor and I heard \"She Loves You\".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 880, "question": "That's great song, didn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 881, "answer": "Amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]